SAARTH KURLE

saarthk11@gmail.com | (628)219-6916 | LinkedIn | GitHub | Website

Summary

As a hardworking and results oriented Web Developer and trained in Full Stack Engineering & ML, I bring a wealth of experience in software development. My expertise extends across the full software development lifecycle, from concept and design to implementation and optimization.

Skills

- Javascript w/ MERN Stack
- Python w/ Data Science
- Java

- MySQL
- Machine Learning
- NLP

Experience

11/2023 - Current The Social Sundays

New York, NY -

Remote

Web Designer and Developer

(Part-Time)

- Translated conceptual designs into responsive and user-friendly websites, amplifying our clients' online presence.
- Specialized in crafting visually captivating and functionally robust websites to meet client needs.
- Played a pivotal role in driving client satisfaction and retention through continuous improvement of website aesthetics and functionality.

08/2022 - 01/2023

CyberCoders
San Francisco, CA

Staff Software Engineer

(Part-Time)

- Worked with a team of 4 engineers on the technical implementation of a web-based platform for a healthcare client, enabling real-time patient data management and collaboration among healthcare providers.
- Created an enterprise-level CRM system for a financial services company. Technologies Used: Node.js, MongoDB, React.js, Java, Spring, PostgreSQL.

10/2021 - 08/2022

Campus Housing -SFSU

San Francisco, CA

Front Desk Assistant

- Assisted residents in various problem-solving scenarios at the front desk of a student dorm building.
- Provided exceptional customer service to ensure a positive living experience for all residents.

06/2021 - 07/2021

Kamal Classes Mumbai, India

Java Developer Apprenticeship

- Completed a Full Stack Advanced Java training program with SQL, JSP, Hibernate Framework and OCJA.
- Completed a MySQL Connected JDBC application with Swings for GUI and JFreecharts as a Final Project.

Education

Expected in 05/2024 **Bachelor of Science** in Computer Science San Francisco, CA San Francisco State University